**y of my stories I'm a starry-eyed romantic on a noble search for true love.
孩子们 在许多故事里我都是个空想浪漫主义者 不屈不挠地寻找真爱
In this one,I'm just a jerk.
但在这个故事中 我只是一混蛋
Well,guys,tonight is the night.
朋友们 就是今晚了
to see my antique camera collection.
我将邀请Tiffany来家里欣赏 我收藏的古董相机
It's Ted's bait.
那是Ted的诱饵
"Bait"?
"诱饵"?
A true gentleman invents a pretense to lure an honorable lady into his apartment.
一个真正的绅士想出来的一个幌子 用来引诱一位尊贵的女士进入他的公寓
Some item of interest or beauty you can both pretend
在她上了你的贼船前五分钟内
to admire for five minutes before she hops on your disco stick.
你可以假装喜欢的一种有趣或美丽的事物
Like she's coming up to "borrow a book" or "check out an album on vinyl.
比如让她来"借本书" "听听老唱片"
" Or to see your new rap poster.
或者"看看你新的饶舌歌手海报"
"Rap poster"?
"饶舌歌手海报"?
Who would that work on?
谁会上那种当?
It was the first week of college.
那是在大学的第一周
I was really into Wu-Tang Clan.
我当时很爱"武当派" (史上最著名的嘻哈团体之一 90年代雄霸美国东岸饶舌乐界)
Yeah,bait is tricky.
是啊 如何下"诱饵"是有技术含量的
It has to be something interesting enough to get the girl upstairs,
要足够有趣 把女生骗上楼
but not so interesting that it overpowers the night.
但假如它在晚上占了主导地位 那就没那么有趣了
BARNEY: I found that a slot machine was too fun.
例如老虎机就好玩过头了
And a trampoline...
而蹦床
turned out to be too dangerous.
又过于危险了
But then I found the perfect bait: a teacup pig.
但是后来我发现了最完美的诱饵: 一只迷你猪
"A teacup pig"?
"迷你猪"?
Who's that working on?
谁又会上那种当?
You have a teacup pig?!
你有迷你猪?!
- I didn't know you had a teacup pig! - Can we see the teacup pig?!
- 我都不知道你有只迷你猪! - 我们能看看迷你猪吗?!
- Hey,can I borrow your teacup pig? - Yes,you can borrow my teacup pig.
- 能把你的迷你猪借我吗? - 行吧 朕借你了
You have a teacup pig?!Oh,my gosh!
你居然有只迷你猪! 苍天啊!
I can't believe you have a teacup pig!
我不敢相信你居然有只迷你猪!
You're just so cute!
你是在太可爱了!
Yes,you are the cutest piggy ever!
是的 你是最最可爱的小猪猪了
What?
什么?
Were you always this pretty?
你总是这么可爱吗?
Or are you going to give me that whole,
你是不是要跟我说那套台词
"Oh,in high school I was really shy and awkward" line?
"噢 高中里我可害羞可笨了"
I was shy and awkward.
我确实害羞又笨
I was,like,a hundred pounds heavier and I had these crazy buck teeth.
当时比现在胖几百斤 还有大暴牙
Seriously?
你说真的?
No,I've always been hot.
不 我一直都这么漂亮
What are you going to do?
能有什么法子呢
Do you know who else would love this teacup pig?
你知道还有谁也爱这迷你猪吗?
My boyfriend.
我的男朋友
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com/=-  Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- 荣誉出品  本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
how.i.met.your.mother. Season 05 Episode 16
老爸老妈的罗曼史 第五季 第16集
YTET-贱猫  -=http://bbs.sfileydy.com/=-
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-  翻译: 午桑 Holah  校对: 猪猡龙龙 浅草懿声 时间轴: 贱猫
You have a boyfriend?
你有男友了?
Ugh,I know.
呃 我知道
So annoying,right?
真烦人 对吧
I mean,he's not really my boyfriend.
我是说 他不算是我的男友
Oh,good.
谢天谢地
I mean,technically,he kind of is.
我是说 理论上说 他又是
Well,is he or isn't he?
那他到底是还不是?
Some of both,but definitely not either.
两种都算 又都不算
Are you getting any of this?
你听明白了吗?
Look,I really like you.
我真的喜欢你
I just need you to be patient.
我只想你能再等等
I don't want to lose you,Big Brown Eyes.
我不想失去你 棕色电眼
Yup.
是啊
Somebody doesn't want to lose Big Brown Eyes.
有人不想失去"棕色电眼"
ROBIN: Oh,Ted.
噢 Ted
She's got you on the hook.
她把你钓上钩了
What?
什么?
What?I'm not on the hook.
啥? 我才没有上钩呢
Oh,you are totally on the hook.
你完完全全上钩了
She's stringing you along.
她把你晾着
She's not committing to you,but she's keeping you around just in case,
又不给你任何承诺 她只拿你当备胎而已
like an old can of chili in the pantry.
就像没菜下饭才会想到的陈年腐乳
Um,who's buying canned chili and not eating it immediately?
买了陈年腐乳的人真会马上吃掉哦?
Amen,sister.
阿门 主啊
Ted,don't feel bad.
Ted 别感到难过
We've all been there.
我们都经历过
I've been on both sides of it.
我两种经历都有
I've been a hookey and a hooker.
我引人上过钩 也上过别人的钩
Move past it,guys.
别八卦我了 大家
I've been a little bit loose,but money never changed hands.
我虽有掉以轻心的时候  但主导权总在我手里
I've been on the hook.
我也上过人家的钩
Lisa Walker.
Lisa Walker
Picture it: 1994,St.Cloud,Minnesota.
我们回到 1994年  明尼苏达州 圣克劳德镇
So I was,like,thinking,Lisa-
我是想 Lisa
do you maybe want to,like,go out with me?
你想 跟我...一起约会吗?
That sounds great.
听起来不错
But I'm sort of seeing this guy.
但是我现在正和一个男孩约会
He's got a LeBaron convertible and an "in" at the roller rink,
他有克莱斯勒男爵敞篷车 和溜冰场的入场券
so I'd hate to burn that bridge.
所以我不想和他断绝关系
I understand.
我明白
But how about this?
这样吧
You can be my secret boyfriend who does all my homework for me.
你可以做帮我做作业的秘密男友
A'ight.
好啊
You want to see my rap poster?
想来看看我的饶舌歌手海报吗?
Poster whore.
你这海报荡妇
MARSHALL: Anyway...
不管怎样
Lisa Walker strung me along for months until one night,
Lisa Walker把我吊了几个月后 直到一天晚上
I went to go tell her how much I loved her.
我去告诉她我有多爱她
In song.
用唱歌的方式
MARSHALL: She wasn't home yet, so I waited.
她还没回家 所以我一直等着
And waited.
等着...
I woke up four hours later,covered in snow.
四小时后我醒了 身上都是积雪
And that's when I saw it.
那时我看到了
Lisa's footsteps.
Lisa的脚印
She had walked right over me and into the house.
她就那样从我身边走进屋里
It was the best thing that could have happened.
那是世界上最好的事情
It got me off her hook.
从此我就摆脱了她的钩子
Okay,that is definitely not what's going on with me and Tiffany.
好吧 这跟我和Tiffany的情况完全不一样
Listen to this.
听着
I'm really into you.
我真的很喜欢你
I just can't be with you right now.
只是目前我不能和你在一起
- Ted,"right no" is the classic on-the-hook catchphrase. - MARSHALL: Yup.
- Ted "目前" 是典型的上钩标语 - 没错
"Right now" paints a picture of some sort of magical future time when everything will work out,
"目前"描绘了一个一切皆有可能的未来
but the truth is,that will never happen.
事实是 那是绝不可能实现的
BARNEY: It's like this.
就像这样
"I can't be with you.
"我不能和你在一起"
" Boom!
轰!
"Right now.
"目前来说"
" LILY: Yeah.
是的
I think my high school boyfriend,Scooter,is still sort of on the hook for me.
我的高中男友 Scooter 现在好像还在我的钩上
Sort of?
好像?
He totally is.
他就是的
The poor guy showed up at our wedding hoping to win you back.
那可怜虫还出现在我们的婚礼上 期待你回心转意
LILY: Yeah.
是的
It's still sometimes weird when I see him at work.
有时在他工作的地方见到他 感觉还是怪怪的
Wait.What?
什么?
Scooter works in the school cafeteria.
Scooter在学校自助餐厅里工作
We've talked about this.
我们已经谈过了
Hey,Lily.Nice dress.
Lily 裙子很漂亮
Tater-tots?
要来点小土豆儿吗? ( 我爱你 )
We most certainly have not talked about this!
我们绝对没有谈过这些!
Yes,we have.
我们有啊
I've mentioned it tons of times.
我提到很多次了
"Lunch Lady Scooter.
"厨娘Scooter"
" I thought that you were referring to some sort of long overdue device
我以为你是指某种早就过时的 (scooter也有摩托车的意思)
that carries around those poor,underappreciated lunch ladies!
载着那些可怜的怀才不遇的厨娘的装置
This explains a lot.
这就难怪了
Lunch Lady Scooter was there again today.
厨娘Scooter今天又来了
Oh,yeah?
是吗?
Did you jump on that thing?
你有没有跳上去
Give it a ride?
骑到它上面?
No!
没有!
Really?
真的?
If it were me,I'd be riding that scooter all day long until I broke that thang in half.
如果是我的话 我会一天到晚骑着它 直到它断成两半(笑死)
So those poor women still have to walk everywhere?
那些可怜的女人还是要徒步到处跑吗
Wait.Scooter is working at your school?!
等一下 Scooter在你们学校工作?
Are you jealous?
你吃醋了?
No,I just feel bad for Scooter.
不 我为Scooter叫屈
'Cause the only reason he took that job is he thinks he has a shot with you.
因为他会在那里工作 唯一的原因是他认为和你还有希望
You have to make it clear that he doesn't,
你必须跟他说明白 他没有机会了
so that he can move on and a real lunch lady can get her job back.Damn!
这样他才能向前看 才能把工作还给一个真正的厨娘 靠
I've tried.
我试过了
Hey,Lily.
Lily
I saw you had seventh period free.
我知道你第七节课休息
So do I.
我也是
You want to run away together?
跟我一起私奔吧?
Let me be clear,Scooter.
我必须跟你说清楚 Scooter
There is no way you and I can ever be together.
我们俩是不可能在一起的
Right now.
目前来说
I'll see you tomorrow,Lily.
明天见 Lily
It's Tijuana Tuesday.
明天是"提华纳的周二"
"Right now"?
"目前来说"?
You right-now'd Scooter?
你对Scooter说"目前来说"?
You need to let Scooter off the hook once and for all.
你必须要让Scooter永久脱离钩子
LILY: You're right.
你说得对
Day after tomorrow,that's exactly what I'm going to do.
我打算后天就跟他摊牌
Why not tomorrow?
为什么明天不说?
Baby,I can't ruin Tijuana Tuesday.
亲爱的 我不能毁了提华纳的周二
Really?
真的吗?
You're really going to sit here all night watching the door
你打算整晚呆坐着看着门
because Tiffany said she'll "try to stop by"?
就因为Tiffany说她会"尽量赶过来"?
Barney,I'm not going to just give up on her.
Barney 我不会就这么放弃她的
NARRATOR: I should have given up on her.
我真应该放弃她的
This girl is special.
这个女孩很特别
She was the devil.
她是恶魔
Things are going to work out with Tiffany.
和Tiffany会有结果的
No,they're not,dumbass.
不 不会有结果的 蠢蛋
Ted,let me be clear: this girl is a poison and you need to cut her out of your life forever.
Ted 我就说白了 这个女人是瓶毒药 你要永远的将她从生活中抹去
Hey,there she is.
她来了
Oh,she brought some of her coworkers.
还带了些同事过来
Hang on to this girl,Ted.
紧紧抓牢这个女孩 Ted
Hang on to her and never let go!
紧紧抓住她 永不放手!
these are some of the hottest girls I've ever seen.
Ted 她们是我见过最漂亮的女人
And they all work with Tiffany?
她们都和Tiffany共事?
Yup.
是的
There could only be one explanation for this.
只有一个原因可以解释了
Ted...
Ted
is Tiffany a ph-ph-ph...
Tiffany是不是医 医 医...
pharmaceutical sales rep?
医药销售代表?
Yeah,how did you know that?
是的 你怎么知道的?
And you never thought to mention that?
你怎么都不说下?
What?It's just a job.
为什么? 这只是份工作
Just a j...
只是份...
just a jah...
只是份工...
Ted,throughout time there has always been one cutting-edge profession to which hot girls,
Ted 一直以来 只有一种顶级职业 聚集了所有辣妹
like Tiffany,have flocked.
就像Tiffany那样的 还成群结队的
Shall I walk you through the history?
要我给你讲一讲历史吗?
- I'm gonna explicitly say no. - It all started 2.5 million years ago.
- 我明确地表示拒绝 - 250万年前
BARNEY: Man was a hunter.
男人是猎人
So,the hottest profession of the day?
史上最辣的职业?
Gatherer.
采摘者
Homo erectus indeed.
的确是猿人(直立--Barney指胸)
As man mastered technology, the hottest profession of the day evolved.
男人进入技术时代 史上最辣的职业莫过于
I'm pretty sure it's a hernia.
我很确定是疝气
Can you check again?
能再查一次吗?
And then,man took to the skies.
然后 男人飞上了天空
And so,hot women put on high heels and became stewardesses.
所以 辣妹穿上了高跟鞋成为了空姐
I am in the upright and locked position.
我已经调节到"垂直锁定"的位置了
And then man said,"Life is hard.
然后男人说 "人生苦短
I should start taking lotsf prescription drugs.
我应该开始服用大量处方药"
" And so,hot girls rolled into doctors' offices,
所以 辣妹们蜂拥到医生办公室
looking sexy enough to render the very erection pills they peddled ironically redundant.
打扮得相当性感 来兜售她们的 勃起小药丸
So now,pharma girls are today's hottest profession.
所以如今 药业就是当今的最辣职业
Hey,Big Brown Eyes.
嗨 棕色电眼
How you doing?
你好吗?
I'm good.
我很好
Hey,by the way,you,uh,you ditch that loser boyfriend yet?
顺便问下 你 你甩了那个废物男友了吗?
No,sir.
没有 先生
Touched my nose.
碰了我的鼻子
Dude,ditch Tiffany and join the Barnacle in a pharma girl free-for-all.
甩了Tiffany 加入Barnacle药业 女孩全场免费
Side effects may include loss of clothing,rug burn,
副作用可能包括衣服丢失 地毯损伤
shortness of breath and sore abdominals the next morning.
呼吸急促 第二天早上腹部疼痛
What in the world is up?!
这世界到底怎么了?!
So...
所以...
I know that you've been having trouble letting Scooter off the hook.
我知道让Scooter下钩不容易
Well,I decided what you need is practice.
好 我决定你需要的就是练习
Now,you say the problem is his cute,sad eyes?
你说问题在于 他那可爱的  楚楚可怜的双眼
Well...
噢...
All right,shut it,woman.
闭嘴 女人
Now,I want you to look at this teacup pig
现在 我要你看着这只迷你猪
and tell him that there's no way that you could ever be with him.
告诉他你们之间绝对没有可能
Teacup Pig,there is no way I can ever be with you.
小猪猪 我们之间没有可能
Right now.
目前来说
come on!Grow a pair!
够了! 成熟点!
I'm sorry,but he's just so freakin' cute.
对不起 但他真的太可爱了
I just want to cuddle him all day long.
让我抱他一整天都行
Yes,I do.
没错 我愿意
You know that's funny.I remember when you used to say things like that about me.
有趣 让我想起你以前也这么对我说过
Oh,I still do.
现在我仍然愿意啊
Yeah,not as much,Lily.
今不如昔了 Lily
Not as much.
今不如昔
Ain't no party like a pharma girl party  'Cause a pharma girl party don't stop!
医药销售女代表的派对是最棒的  因为它不会停止!
Dude,I have already hooked up with three of them.
哥们 我已经搞定三个了
Fantasmo.
棒极了
Plus,my cholesterol is down.
还有 我的胆固醇降低了
My restless legs syndrome is cured.
腿部不宁症治好了
I've never felt more alive- oh.
我从来没感到生命如此鲜活
Guys,great news.
好消息
Tiffany broke up with her boyfriend.
Tiffany终于和她男友分手
Proof that I am not on the hook.
就此证明了 我没上钩
Oh,you're still on the hook.
你还是上钩了
Ah,uh-uh,listen to how we spent last night.
先听听昨晚我们怎么过
First,we cuddled.
首先 我们拥抱
Then,we shared chocolate cake.
然后 我们一起吃巧克力蛋糕
Then,well,I don't usually join in on locker room talk,
之后 虽然我不常参加更衣室谈话 (炫耀性事的场所)
but I gave her a pretty sensual foot rub.
但我给她妙不可言的揉脚
And let me guess: it didn't go any further than that.
我猜猜 事情就到此为止了
Well,no,but...
嗯 不尽然 不过...
And tell me,did you by any chance make that chocolate cake?
告诉我 那巧克力蛋糕是你做的吗?
- It was a mix. - Dude.
我有负责搅拌
There's no shame in admitting it,Ted.
没有必要羞于承认 Ted
We've all been on people's hooks and we've all kept someone on the hook.
我们都曾上过钩 也让别人上我们的钩
Um,I most certainly have not.
我就没有过
What?!Are you joking?
什么?! 开什么玩笑?
What about that girl from the university library?
还记得那个大学图书馆的女生吗?
Um, Henrietta?
Henrietta?
Henrietta and I are just friends.
Henrietta和我只是朋友
Oh, she is so on your hook.
她上你钩上大发了
Absolutely not.
当然不是
NARRATOR:She totally was.
她确实上我的钩了
I mean...
我是说...
we cuddled.
我们相拥
We shared chocolate cake.
分享巧克力蛋糕
She gave me foot rubs- long ones.
给我做脚部按摩 -时间颇长
I'm not proud,kids.
孩子们 我很惭愧
You like having Henrietta around for the same reason that Tiffany likes having you around:
你和Henrietta的相处方式 正如Tiffany那样
it's a nice little ego boost.
不过是些自我膨胀的产物而已
No wonder you're such an expert about keeping people on the hook.
怪不得你在这方面是个专家
What about that poor camera guy you work with?
还记得那个被你愚弄的摄像师?
Mike and I are just friends.
Mike和我只是朋友
Come on.
吹吧你
Oh,yeah,that's the stuff.
就是那里
Robin,have you ever thought about taking us to the next level?
Robin 你有想过让我们之间更进一步吗?
Well,if you're talking about doing my laundry,I'm on board.
如果你说的是帮我洗衣服 没问题
You got yourself a deal.
是你说的啊
What?!
什么?!
I- I am not keeping Mike on the hook.
我才没有让Mike上钩呢
You are Captain Hook.
你简直是铁钩船长
Dude,I'm a girl.
我是个女孩
Okayour girl parts are like a spiderweb.
女孩子就像蜘蛛网
Sometimes you're gonna catch stuff you don't want.
总会有些你不喜欢的东西撞上来
That doesn't make it okay.
这不成理由
Oh,a-and Henrietta is in,in no way wasting her time with you,right?
那Henrietta还不是 在你身上浪费她的青春?
Henrietta knows that we're just friends.
Henrietta清楚我们是朋友
In fact,I'm gonna call her up and hang out with her tonight as friends.
这样吧 我现在就打给她  像朋友一样度过今晚
Hey,Ted.
嘿 Ted
I love you.
我爱你
What?
什么?
Uh,do you want a foot massage?
要我给你揉脚吗?
'Cause I've been practicing on myself.
我有在自己身上练习过哦
No,I'm good.
不了
I didn't know if you were hungry,so I just threw together some...
不知道你饿不饿 所以擅自准备了些...
it's not a big deal.
粗茶淡饭啦
Kids,looking back,I don't know how I didn't see that Henrietta was madly in love with me.
孩子们  回想当初我不知为何 我对Henrietta爱我的事实毫无知觉
Hello.
喂
Hey,Ted.
嘿 Ted
Hey,Tiffany.
嘿 Tiffany
I'm going out of town this weekend for my friend's wedding.
这周末我要参加朋友的婚礼
Want to be my date?
要当我的伴吗?
I would love to.
非常愿意
Hey,what are you doing right now?
现在在干嘛呢?
Oh,God,no.
不是吧
Awesome.
好极了
Okay,I'll see you in,like,ten minutes?
十分钟后见好吗?
Great.
好极了
Soy,Henrietta,something came up.
不好意思 Henrietta 有点事
Take a rain check,pal?
延期再续好吗? 哥们
Yeah,it's no problem.
没问题
All right,yeah,hey-ho.
哼哼哈嘿
Oh,you're strong.
你真壮~
What a jerk.
我是个混蛋
Henrietta,I...
Henrietta 我...
Wait.Where did Ted go?
等等 Ted呢?
I thought we were finally going to get to meet him.
不是说要见家长了吗?
Yeah,something came up,okay,Mom?
他有点事 就这样了 妈
I told you there was no Ted.
早告诉你没有什么Ted
I heard that.
我能听到
So there I was,at one of the surest signs of taking a relationship to the next level:
就这样 带着对 关系更进一步的征兆的憧憬
an out-of-town wedding.
婚礼伴侣
It was finally happening.
终于到了那一天
Champagne?
香槟?
Ted,oh,my gosh,I forgot to call you.
Ted 天呐 我忘了打给你
Well,whatever it is you wanted to talk about,we can talk about it now.
你可以现在跟我说
This is Jack.
这是Jack
He's the best man at the wedding.
他是婚礼的伴郎
We just got back together.
我们刚复合
You know,now that I think about it,a phone call would have been nice.
现在想想 这事电话上跟我说比较好
You're Ted?
你就是Ted?
Ouch.
哎呀
But I hear you make a mean chocolate cake.
不过听说你做巧克力蛋糕不咋地
Oh,isn't he great?
他很棒是吧?
And he's in a band.
而且他组了个乐队哦
Thanks.
谢谢
Come on,Lily.
快 Lily
You have to get Scooter off the hook.
别再愚弄Scooter了
Now,try again.
再试试
Teacup Pig,oh...
迷你猪...
I don't want to be with you.
我不想跟你在一起
Right now.
目前来说
Man up!
再来!
Teacup Pig...
迷你猪...
I don't want to be with you.
我不想跟你在一起
Ever.
永远都不
Finish him!
说完它!
We will never be together in any sort of sexual way ever again.
我们之间不会再有任何情爱关系
Nice.
好
Sort of a weird thing to say to a pig.
就是跟头猪这么说有点怪
It felt really wrong.
怪死了
Anyway,I just don't think you and I are going to work.
总而言之 我不觉得我们之间有可能
Right now.
目前来说
NARRATOR:And that's when it hit me.
就这样我清醒过来
I was on the hook.
我确实上了钩
I also realized...
同时我意识到...
I missed this so much, baby.
亲爱的 这太让我怀念了
...Tiffany was on this guy's hook.
...Tiffany上了这家伙的钩
It was a vicious cycle.
真是个恶性循环
Henrietta was on my hook.
Henrietta上了我钩
And years later, I found out this poor bastard was on Henrietta's hook.
多年之后 我发现 这混蛋上了Henrietta的钩
You know what?
知道吗?
We're not going to work ever.
我们之间永远没可能
I'm done. I'm done.
我受够了
And it's really better for the circulation
试试用拇指揉揉足弓
if you knead the arches with your thumbs.
对血液循环有好处
Now, I'm done.
我说完了
Marshall, I can do this by myself.
Marshall 我自己一个可以了
Okay, well, then prove it.
那就证明给我看
And, um...
还有...
Grab me a pudding.
帮我带个布丁
Listen up, Scooter.
听着 Scooter
There is no way you and I will ever be together.
我们之间绝对没可能
Right now!Marshall!
目前来说! Marshall!
I'm sorry, but he's adorable.
对不起 可是他太可爱了
Listen.
听着
I don't want to be with you.
我不想跟你在一起
Right now.Hang in there, Scoots!
目前来说 坚持住! Scoots!
I'm not going to live forever.
我们不会永远在一起的
Last night I was with this pharma girl who was so hot,
昨晚那个药品代理女郎实在是太辣了
you should call a doctor if you don't have an erection for more than four hours.
要是你不连续勃起四小时就该打给医院了
Am I right, people?
是吧 兄弟?
Yeah, there's no people-
没有什么兄弟-
just the girl you most recently dated.
只有个最近跟你刚分手的女人
Hey,Barney.
嘿 Barney
I want you to meet the newest pharma girl.
给你介绍我们药品代理的新人
Gladys Reynolds.
Gladys Reynolds
Nice to make your acquaintance.
很高兴认识你
I represent statins and other cholesterol-lowering drugs.
我代理的是抑制素和降胆固醇药
Come on,girl.Let's go get our drink on.
来吧 咱们去喝个够
It's over.
结束了
What's over?
什么结束了?
Pharma girls are no longer exclusively hot chicks.
药品代理不再是辣妹的代名词
It's the en.
这是时代的终结
You're being a little dramatic.
你有点小题大做了
Am I?
我?
It starts out with a Gladys.
这会从那个Gladys开始
Next thing you know,a few not-so-fabulous gay guys enter the ranks.
然后 一些不咋地的基情男会进入这行业
And before you know it,
你还没意识过来
pharma girls look like the crew on a Southwest flight from Albuquerque to Little Rock.
药品代理女郎就会像阿尔伯克基 到小石城的西南航空机组人员一样
It's over!
结束了!
So that night,I went straight to Henrietta's- all set to let her off the hook.
那晚 我去到Henrietta家 准备好让她清醒过来
This is Jack.
这是Jack
He's the best man at the wedding.
他是婚礼的伴郎
I'm done.
我受够了
Yes!
我愿意!
The answer is yes!
答案是 我愿意!
No.
不是吧
it gets worse.
祸不单行
It's perfect!
太合适了!
Mom,Dad!
妈妈爸爸!
Ted proposed!
Ted向我求婚了!
Oh,my God!
我的天!
I knew this day would come!
我就知道会有这么一天!
Son!
儿子!
Yeah,well,there's been a...
这个 那个 是个误...
No.
不是吧
What did you do?
你怎么办?
I seriously considered just marrying her out of sheer awkwardness.
相对于尴尬 我有考虑过就这么婚了
But I did what I had to do.
不过我做了正确的事
I did what anyone keeping someone on the hook should do.
任何有备胎的人都会做的事
I broke her heart.
我伤了她的心
Henrietta,I'm sorry if this is blunt,but I think I owe you this.
Henrietta 或许这样太直接  不过我想该跟你说
I don't want to be with you.
我不想跟你在一起
Right now?
目前来说?
Ever.
永远
But we're still getting married,right?
不过我们还是会结婚 对吧?
It was brutal.
真是太残忍了
Oh,I'm sorry,buddy.
真遗憾 伙计
Honesty is tough,but in the end,it is the far kinder alternative.
真话确实会伤人 不过终究是个好的选择
Yeah.
没错
Hey,sweetie.
嘿 宝贝
Hey,Mike.
嘿 Mike
I have to tell you something.
有些事要跟你说
Wait.Did you finish my delicates?
等等 我的内衣你洗了没?
Got one more load.
等下再洗
it can wait.
慢慢来没问题
I...
我...
Hey,how's it going?
怎么样啦?
Still in mourning over the end of the pharma girl era?
还在为药品代理女郎时代终结而伤心吗?
No.
不
I realized that their reign had to end to make room for some new hot girl profession.
我明白 她们需要让出霸主地位 给其他火辣的职业女性
Maybe it'll be intergalactic communications officer on a rocket ship
可能会是在无法想象的远方星系里的
to some distant solar system we can't possibly imagine.
宇宙船星际通信员
Maybe it'll be...
可能是...
meter maids.We just don't know.
女交警 没人知道
But one thing is sure.
不过有件事是肯定的
The future glows like a giant sun shooting amber rays of light into our hearts and minds.
未来正如太阳射出琥珀色的光线 照在我心田
Wow,uh,what changed your mind?
是什么改变了你的心态?
The realization that hope springs eternal,Robin.
人类总是向往美好事物的 Robin
That and this little bottle of purple pills I found in my couch cushion.
同时还有藏在我沙发下的一瓶紫色小药丸
Don't know what they are,but they are amazing!
不知道什么成分 不过感觉好极了
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com/=-  Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- 荣誉出品  本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径